http://www.rookiesports.co.uk/pages/contact-us/privacy-policy.php

Our customers
Why Rookie Sports?
FAQ
This privacy policy sets out how Rookie Sports uses and protects
any information that you give Rookie Sports when you use this website.
Rookie Sports is committed to ensuring that your privacy is
protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you
can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that
it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Rookie Sports may change this policy from time to time by updating
this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that
you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1st May 2012.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name and job title
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you
with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products,
special offers or other information which we think you may find
interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you
for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or
mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to
your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In
order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place
suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard
and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your
computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie
helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular
site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual.
The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and
dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your
preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used.
This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website
in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information
for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the
system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by
enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not.
A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information
about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers
automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser
setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from
taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However,
once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that
we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot
be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which
you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed
by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the
privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for
the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the
information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information
for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by
writing to or emailing us at info@rookiesports.co.uk
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to
third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to
do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional
information about third parties which we think you may find interesting
if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about
you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If
you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Rookie Sports, Suite 4, John Buddle Work Village, Buddle Road, Newcastle upon Tyne. NE4 8AW
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is
incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible
at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to
be incorrect.
:
About Us ::
Terms and Conditions ::
Sitemap
:: Privacy Policy
:: Disclaimer ::
FAQs
::
Facebook
::
Twitter:
Coded with validXHTML, CSS and tested for WCAG Priority 2 Conformance.
Powered by Website Baker, design by gavjof
